{
    "id": "3304b5ca50674eb88617823c29ab4164",
    "title": "This, That, These And Those",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "2ea73ba2151e41329efdffb95481337e",
            "title": "This, That, These And Those",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "................................... were the best days of my life.",
                    "description": "That and those refer to situations that are over.",
                    "answers": [
                        "Those",
                        "That",
                        "These"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "………………………. says that he wants to watch a movie.",
                    "description": "This cannot be used without a noun when it refers to people.",
                    "answers": [
                        "This",
                        "This boy",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Put …………………….. down – they are dirty.",
                    "description": "When this, that, these and those refer to things, they can be used with or without articles.",
                    "answers": [
                        "those",
                        "those clothes",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "………………………… is very tasty. Can I have some more?",
                    "description": "We use this to talk about people and things which are close to us.",
                    "answers": [
                        "This",
                        "That",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Get ……………………….. cat off the piano.",
                    "description": "We use that and those to talk about people and things which are away from us.",
                    "answers": [
                        "this",
                        "that",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I don’t know what I am doing in ……………………. company.",
                    "description": "Here the present continuous verb clearly indicates that we are talking about something that is going on at the moment. We use this and these in these contexts.",
                    "answers": [
                        "this",
                        "that",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "All the time I worked at …………………….. company I hated it.",
                    "description": "That and those refer to situations that are over.",
                    "answers": [
                        "this",
                        "that",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "You shouldn’t have behaved like ……………………….",
                    "description": "That and those refer to situations that are over.",
                    "answers": [
                        "this",
                        "that",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "A dog’s intelligence is much greater than ………………………..",
                    "description": "That and those are often used with a following description to mean ‘the ones’.",
                    "answers": [
                        "a cat",
                        "that of a cat",
                        "this of a cat"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "…………………….. who have not yet registered should do so immediately.",
                    "description": "Those who means the people who. These cannot be used with this meaning.",
                    "answers": [
                        "Those",
                        "These",
                        "That"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "It was so cold ………………………… I could see my breath.",
                    "description": "We use that in the conjunction so…that.",
                    "answers": [
                        "that",
                        "this",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "‘How was the movie?’ ‘Not all ………………………. good.’",
                    "description": "Not all that can mean not very.",
                    "answers": [
                        "that",
                        "this"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}